Finding Aid for the Louis Thurston Nicholas Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- PROGRAMS NASHVILLE SYMPHONY ORCHESTRA, (Programs for 1967 to 1975 with Thor Johnson as Conductor are in the Thor Johnson Series) The conductors of the NSO: William Strickland (1946-1951) Guy Taylor (1951-1959), Willis Page (1959-1967) Thor Johnson (1967-1975), Michael Charry (1976-1982) and Kennet
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Program—Jack Daniel’s Original Silver Cornet Band benefiting the Nashville Symphony (Box 217, Folder 13))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Four Quintets by Donald Erb—Sarratt Performing Arts Committee, Feb. 13, 1983 (Box 217, Folder 14))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Programs, Feb. 3, 1963- Nov. 8, 1980, Feb. 4, 1985 (Box 217, Folder 15))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Press information on Michael Semanitzky— George Peabody College, School of Music (Box 218, Folder 1))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials (Box 218, Folder 2))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Press information—Newspaper articles (Box 218, Folder 3))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials—Oct. 1965-1976 (Box 218, Folder 4))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials (Box 218, Folder 5))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials (Box 218, Folder 6))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials (Box 218, Folder 7))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials—1955- April 1995 (Box 218, Folder 8))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials—1956-1965 (Box 218, Folder 9))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials—1966-1969—Brochures—Willis Page, Music Director, 1965-67; Tennessean clipping, Oct. 22, 1965 “Symphony Eyes Ford Aid”; “Symposium, World Premiere Nov. 24, 1969, L. N. Panel Narrator” (Box 218, Folder 10))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials, Jan. 29, 1975 – Aug. 28, 1975 (Box 218, Folder 11))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Materials including Alfred Bartles’ world premiere performance of Music for Jazz Ensemble and Symphony Orchestra, April 4 and 5, 1966 (Box 218, Folder 12))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Orchestra List 1957-58; A-B-C’s of Symphonies (Box 218, Folder 13))
  - Nashville Symphony News, April 1957, Jan. 1958; Oct. 1958; Dec. 1963; March 1969; Oct. 1969; Nov. 1969; Jan. 1972 (Box 218, Folder 14))
  - Nashville Symphony News, Nov. 1985; 1993-1996 (Box 218, Folder 15))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Publications—Nashville Symphony Notes, Nov. 1977; Feb. 1979; Nov. 1982; April 1983; Symphony Score, Fall 1980 (Box 218, Folder 16))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra Notes, Nov. 1981; March 1982; Winter 1985 (Box 218, Folder 17))
  - Nashville Symphony Association—Memorandum, Oct. 27, 1980; 1983-84; String Quartet and Lecture by Walter Sharp; Nashville Chamber Players—Photograph from The Tennessean, 4-24-71 (Box 218, Folder 18))
  - Nashville Symphony String Quartet—L.N.’s review in The Tennessean—, Nov. 5, 1963 (Box 218, Folder 19))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Newspaper clippings, March 1966; April 1966 (Box 218, Folder 20))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Repertoire 1970-1981, Subscription Concerts (18 pages) (Box 218, Folder 21))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Nashville Youth Orchestra, May 1955;Memorandum RE: Nashville Youth Symphony July 14, 1972; Program--Nashville Symphony String Quartet Presented by Peabody College, April 20, 1955 (Box 218, Folder 22))
  - Nashville Symphony Chorus, Nashville Symphony Chamber Players; Nashville String Quartet—Programs (Box 218, Folder 23))
- PROGRAMS NASHVILLE COLLEGE AND UNIVERSITY, MESSIAH, AND THEATRE
  - Belmont College—Programs and Promotional Materials, April 28, 1952 –May 31, 1959 (Box 219, Folder 1))
  - Belmont College—Programs and Promotional Materials, March 1, 1960—Dec. 16, 1969 (Box 219, Folder 2))
  - Belmont College—Programs and Promotional Materials, 1970- Nov. 20, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 3))
  - Belmont College—Programs and Promotional Materials, Sept. 24, 1980—Nov. 24, 1985 (Box 219, Folder 4))
  - Belmont College—Programs, Jan. 13, 1986—Nov. 18, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 5))
  - Belmont College—Programs, Jan. 23, 1990—Feb. 9, 1992 (Box 219, Folder 6))
  - Belmont College—Programs, Feb. 25, 1992—Nov. 15, 1993 (Box 219, Folder 7))
  - Belmont College—Programs, Jan. 11, 1994—Dec. 11, 1995 (Box 219, Folder 8))
  - Belmont College—Programs, Jan. 15, 1996—Nov. 10, 1997 (Box 219, Folder 9))
  - Belmont College—Programs, Feb. 17, 1998—Nov. 9-12, 2000 (Box 220, Folder 1))
  - Belmont College—Programs, Jan. 31, 2000 – April 29, 2002 (Box 220, Folder 2))
  - Belmont College, School of Music—Programs—(No date) (Box 220, Folder 3))
  - Belmont College, School of Music—Programs—Friends of Chamber Music (Box 220, Folder 4))
  - Belmont College, School of Music—Programs—Friends of Chamber Music (Box 220, Folder 5))
  - Belmont College, School of Music—Programs—Friends of Music (Box 220, Folder 6))
  - Belmont College, School of Music—Programs—Music News—Spring 1983 –, Fall 1996 (Box 220, Folder 7))
  - Belmont College, School of Music—Promotional Materials –1954—1970’s, Dec. 8, 1985 (Box 220, Folder 8))
  - Belmont College, School of Music—Programs and Promotional Materials, 1961-1971 (Box 220, Folder 9))
  - Belmont College, School of Music—Tennessean reviews by L. N., (1966) (Box 220, Folder 10))
  - Ward Belmont Conservatory of Music—Programs—Stetson Humphrey, Elizabeth Baber; Lawrence Goodman (Box 220, Folder 11))
  - Blair Academy of Music—Programs, May 29, 1966—Dec. 1, 1974 (Box 221, Folder 1))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Feb. 14, 1965—Oct. 27, 1969 (Box 221, Folder 2))
  - Blair Academy of Music/Blair School of Music—Programs, 1970-Oct. 21, 1979 (Box 221, Folder 3))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Feb. 14, 1980—Oct. 23, 1983 (Box 221, Folder 4))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Jan. 9, 1984 –Dec. 10, 1986 (Box 221, Folder 5))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Jan. 18, 1987—Nov. 18,1989 (Box 221, Folder 6))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Jan. 28, 1990- Nov. 20, 1992 (Box 221, Folder 7))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Jan. 29, 1993- Nov. 14, 1993 (Box 221, Folder 8))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Feb. 15, 1994—Dec. 3, 1995 (Box 221, Folder 9))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Jan. 14, 1996—Nov. 20, 1996 (Box 221, Folder 10))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Feb. 4, 1997—Nov. 20, 1997 (Box 221, Folder 11))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs—“Virtuosity and the Art of Transcription” 1997 Festival of the American Liszt Society, Oct. 9-11, 1997 (Box 221, Folder 12))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Jan. 11, 1998-Dec. 1, 1998 (Box 221, Folder 13))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Feb. 9, 1999- Nov. 13,1999 (Box 221, Folder 14))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs, Jan. 28, 2000—2002, 2003 (and undated) (Box 221, Folder 15))
  - Blair School of Music—Programs—Nashville Area Music Teachers Association, Oct. 11, 1981-May 8, 1983 (Box 221, Folder 16))
  - Blair School of Music—Faculty—Enid Katahn (Box 222, Folder 1))
  - Blair School of Music-Bulletins, Calendars, Information, 1964-1970 (Box 222, Folder 2))
  - Blair School of Music-Bulletins, Calendars, and Information—1970’s (Box 222, Folder 3))
  - Blair School of Music—Press Release Information—Blair Academy of Music (Box 222, Folder 4))
  - Blair School of Music—Program—Fanfare for the Uncommon Woman—A Symposium, April 15-17, 1993 (Box 222, Folder 5))
  - Blair School of Music—Program—“Building a Stairway to Paradise: American Popular Music 1890-1940” by Mark Wait, Dean, Reunion Weekend, May 23, 1997 (Box 222, Folder 6))
  - Blair School of Music—Program—October 1997—Festival of the American Liszt Society (Box 222, Folder 7))
  - Blair School of Music—Program—“Of Bare Feet and Bared Souls, A Retrospective of 20th Century Music” by Michael Alec Rose, 1998-2000 (Box 222, Folder 8))
  - Blair School of Music—Blair Quarternote Spring 1986; Summer 1997; Concert Series 1997/98; Blair School of Music; Vanderbilt University (photo of Violinist Christian Teal, p. 2) (Box 222, Folder 9))
  - Blair School of Music –Newspaper Articles/Reviews in The Tennessean by L.N. (Box 222, Folder 10))
  - Blair School of Music—Article on “Blair Quartet: Rhodes Premier” by L.N. in Musical America August, 1980 (Box 222, Folder 11))
  - Fisk University—Programs— Glee Club, Dec. 8, 1928 (Box 223, Folder 1))
  - Fisk University—Programs, Jan. 3, 1931—March 8, 1939 (Box 223, Folder 2))
  - Fisk University—Programs, Dec. 14, 1940—May 9, 1948 (Box 223, Folder 3))
  - Fisk University—Programs, May 7, 1950- Dec. 7, 1955 (Box 223, Folder 4))
  - Fisk University—Programs, Feb. 16, 1956—Feb. 28, 1959 (Box 223, Folder 5))
  - Fisk University—Programs, Feb. 6, 1960—Dec. 15, 1962 (Box 223, Folder 6))
  - Fisk University—Programs, March 5, 1963—Dec. 1, 1964 (Box 223, Folder 7))
  - Fisk University—Programs, Feb. 24, 1965—Dec. 12, 1967 (Box 223, Folder 8))
  - Fisk University—Programs, 1968-Dec. 7, 1969 (Box 223, Folder 9))
  - Fisk University—Programs, March 2, 1970—May 26, 1972 (Box 223, Folder 10))
  - Fisk University—Programs, Feb. 1973—March 14, 1976 (Box 223, Folder 11))
  - Fisk University—Programs, Nov. 29, 1981; Sept. 8, 1983; Nov. 6, 1988 (Box 223, Folder 12))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Undated (Box 223, Folder 13))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Undated (Box 223, Folder 14))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Tennessean articles by L.N. and others (Box 223, Folder 15))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Tennessean articles by L.N. and others (Box 223, Folder 16))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Tennessean articles by L.N. and others (Box 223, Folder 17))
  - Fisk University—Newspaper article, July 14, 1957 on President Stephen Wright and Invitation on occasion of his Inauguration, April 1958 (Box 223, Folder 18))
  - Fisk University—Programs-Dance, 1964, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 19))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Festival of Music and Art, 1952, 1953, 1954, 1955, 1956 (Box 224, Folder 1))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Festival of Music and Art, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961 (Box 224, Folder 2))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Festival of Music and Art, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965 (Box 224, Folder 3))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Festival of Music and Art, 1966, 1967, 1969 (Box 224, Folder 4))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Arts Festival, 1968, 1970, 1971, 1972 (Box 224, Folder 5))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Arts Festival, 1973, 1974, 1975, 1976, 1988 (Box 224, Folder 6))
  - Fisk University—92nd Commencement Program, June 3-7, 1966 (Box 224, Folder 7))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Department of Music,1935- May 20, 1967 (including programs by L.N. and S.L.N. June 29, 1945 April 1953; Tennessean review, Oct. 27, 1965, Feb. 10, 1966 (Box 224, Folder 8))
  - Fisk University—Programs, May 9, 1974 –Oct. 19, 1979 (Box 224, Folder 9))
  - Fisk University—Programs—Annual Concert Series, 1950, 1951, 1957-58 (Box 224, Folder 10))
  - Fisk University—Annual Concert Series, 1963-1969, 1974-75, 1975-76 (Box 224, Folder 11))
  - Fisk University—Promotional Materials—Pianist John Ogden and others (Box 224, Folder 12))
  - Fisk University—Programs and promotional materials (Box 224, Folder 13))
  - Fisk University—See Nashville Symphony Orchestra Box 217, Folder 12 “A Concert of Works by Negro Composers” William Dawson, guest conductor, Fisk Memorial Chapel (Box 224, Folder 14))
  - Austin Peay State University—Programs—April 2, 1954, Nov. 3, 1987 (Box 225, Folder 1))
  - Austin Peay State University---Programs, Nov. 16, 1988 – April 4, 1994 (Box 225, Folder 2))
  - Austin Peay State University—Calendar of Events (Box 225, Folder 3))
  - David Lipscomb College—Programs, April 8, 1948—Dec. 22, 1959 (Box 225, Folder 4))
  - David Lipscomb College—Programs, Jan. 7, 1960-Nov. 3, 1969 (Box 225, Folder 5))
  - David Lipscomb College—Programs, May 11, 1970—Sept. 29, 1975 (Box 225, Folder 6))
  - David Lipscomb College—Programs, Jan. 20, 1980—Oct. 10, 1989 (Box 225, Folder 7))
  - David Lipscomb College—Programs, 1990- Dec. 7, 1999 (Box 225, Folder 8))
  - David Lipscomb College—Programs, Jan. 27, 2000- Sept. 17, 2002 (Box 225, Folder 9))
  - David Lipscomb College—Programs—Undated (Box 225, Folder 10))
  - East Tennessee State University—Programs, April 15, 1955—June 1971 (Box 225, Folder 11))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs, June 1, 1954—Dec. 13, 1969 (Box 225, Folder 12))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs, Jan. 9, 1971 –April 29, 1977 (Box 225, Folder 13))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs, Jan. 22, 1981—Oct. 18, 1986 (Box 225, Folder 14))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs, May 5, 1992—March 8, 1999 (Box 225, Folder 15))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs—Student Recitals, 1958-1974 (Box 225, Folder 16))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs—Student Recitals, 1975- 1985 (Box 226, Folder 1))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs—Student Recitals, 1986-undated (Box 226, Folder 2))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs, Dec. 13, 1963; Nov. 11, 1966; Dec. 9, 1966; Dec. 12, 1966; April 27, 1969; Dec. 11, 1970; April 23, 1972 (Box 226, Folder 3))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs—Sarah Lacey Nicholas Artist Series—March 30, 2000; Feb. 20, 2001; Oct. 25, 2001; Sept. 2002—Inaugural Gala Concert for Mathew Pinson, 5th President (Box 226, Folder 4))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Programs—Commencement Exercises May 1972; An Evening of Music, Nov. 11, 1966 (Box 226, Folder 5))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College-Alumni News 1985; Spring Supplement 1985; Bulletin March 1969; Bulletin, September/October 1973 (Box 226, Folder 6))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Pauline Writings by Robert Picirilli, 1967 (Box 226, Folder 7))
  - Free Will Baptist Bible College—Stationery (Box 226, Folder 8))
  - Middle Tennessee State University—Programs, Dec. 15, 1947—1995 (Box 226, Folder 9))
  - —Programs—Worship Hour (Box 226, Folder 10) Nashville University Center (Vanderbilt, Peabody, Scarritt))
  - Nashville University Center Council—Calendars (Box 226, Folder 11))
  - Nashville University Center—Fine Arts Committee—Catalog, 1973-75 (Box 226, Folder 12))
  - Nashville University Center—Promotional Materials (Box 226, Folder 13))
  - Scarritt College—Programs, June 6, 1935 –Dec. 12, 1965 (Box 226, Folder 14))
  - Scarritt College—Programs, May 22, 1970—May 8, 1979 (Box 226, Folder 15))
  - Scarritt College—Programs, May 7, 1981—April 17, 1988 (Box 226, Folder 16))
  - Scarritt College—Programs, April 15, 1990-Dec. 10, 1995 (Box 226, Folder 17))
  - Scarritt College—Programs, March 24, 1996—Sept. 16, 2001 (Box 227, Folder 1))
  - Scarritt College—The Scarritt Bulletin, 1984-86 (Box 227, Folder 2))
  - Tennessee A and I State University—Programs, 1950-1959 (Box 227, Folder 3))
  - Tennessee A and I State University—Programs—Jan. 30, 1961-March 24, 1969 and Tennessean Review by L. N. (Box 227, Folder 4))
  - Tennessee A and I State University Department of Music—Program—Composers Workshop in Class Project Performance, May 30, 1968; Letter Jan. 28, 1969 (Box 227, Folder 5))
  - Tennessee State University—Programs, April 15, 1952--Nov. 1967 (Box 227, Folder 6))
  - Tennessee State University—Programs, March 1969-Feb. 1999, undated (Box 227, Folder 7))
  - Tennessee State University—Program—Rotterdam Philharmonic—April 7, 1970; Volunteer State Comm. College, Music Dept. March 10, 1981; Univ. of Tennessee, Nashville—April 15, 1973; UT, Feb. 25, 1986 (Box 227, Folder 8))
  - Trevecca Nazarene College—Music Department—Programs, 1946-1978 (Box 227, Folder 9))
  - Trevecca Nazarene College—Programs, Feb. 5, 1982—Oct. 20, 1989 (Box 227, Folder 10))
  - Trevecca Nazarene College—Programs, Jan. 26, 1990--Dec. 8, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 11))
  - Trevecca Nazarene College—Dept. of Music—Programs, Feb. 1,1991—Dec. 9, 1991 (Box 227, Folder 12))
  - Trevecca Nazarene College-Dept. of Music—Programs—Spring, 1992-April 14, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 13))
  - Trevecca Nazarene College—Dept. of Music—Handbook, 1983—1984 (Box 227, Folder 14))
  - Trevecca Nazarene College—Dept. of Music—Handbook, 1988- 1989 (Box 227, Folder 15))
  - Trevecca Nazarene College—Lesson Sheets and Performance Evaluation Forms (Box 227, Folder 16))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Programs, March 8, 1955 –July 1959 (Box 228, Folder 1))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Programs, July 1960—July 12, 1964 (Box 228, Folder 2))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Programs, 1965—July 19, 1969 (Box 228, Folder 3))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Programs, June 21, 1970—July 20, 1975 (Box 228, Folder 4))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Programs—undated (Box 228, Folder 5))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Programs Summer Music Festival, 1960,1961, 1962, 1963, 1965 (Box 228, Folder 6))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Programs—Summer Music Festival, 1961, 1966, 1968, 1969 (Box 228, Folder 7))
  - University of the South at Sewanee---Programs—Summer Music Festival, 1970-1977 (missing 1974) (Box 228, Folder 8))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Programs—Summer Music Center Information Brochure, 1982-1989; 1992; 2000 (Box 228, Folder 9))
  - University of the South at Sewanee— Program information--Sewanee Concert Series, (1969, 1972, 1982-83) (Box 228, Folder 10))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—1970 Gift Income Report; Report August 31, 1972; “Sewanee Vintage, June 1956” “Campaign for Sewanee, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 11))
  - University of the South at Sewanee—Music Events—Newspaper Reviews in The Tennessean by L.N. (Box 228, Folder 12))
  - University of Tennessee—Commencement Program—Memphis, Tn, March 21, 1965 (Box 228, Folder 13))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs—Cap and Bells Club, May 1928, May 1930 (Box 229, Folder 1))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs, March 5, 1931—May 10, 1938 (Box 229, Folder 2))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs, Dec. 1947—1959 (Box 229, Folder 3))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs, March 20, 1960—June 2, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 4))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs, Sept. 5, 1964—Oct. 27, 1968 (Box 229, Folder 5))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs, April 27, 1970—1979 (Box 229, Folder 6))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs, Dec. 6, 1981—May 11, 2000 and undated (Box 229, Folder 7))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs—Cathedral Singers (Box 229, Folder 8))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs—Chamber Music Series, Underwood Auditorium, Nov. 15, 1964—Nov. 16, 1969 (Box 229, Folder 9))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs—Chamber Music Series, Underwood Auditorium, Feb. 8, 1970—Sept. 30, 1973 (Box 229, Folder 10))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs—Chamber Music Series, Underwood Auditorium, Jan. 13, 1974-1978 (Box 229, Folder 11))
  - Vanderbilt University—Great Performances at Vanderbilt—Programs and Promotional Materials (Box 229, Folder 12))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs—Friends of Chamber Music, Feb. 18, 1962—Feb. 2, 1964 (Box 229, Folder 13))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs—Theatre Nashville at VU Theater, 1967-1970 (Box 229, Folder 14))
  - Vanderbilt University—Programs—Athenian Sing, 1960, 1961, 1965 (Box 229, Folder 15))
  - Vanderbilt University—L.N.’s reviews of Vanderbilt programs (Box 229, Folder 16))
  - Messiah— Programs—Calvary Episcopal Church of Memphis featuring L.N., (1942, 43, 45, 46, 47, 48, 1951) (Box 230, Folder 1))
  - Messiah*--Programs—Presentations by Community Chorus and Peabody Orchestra featuring Louis Nicholas, (1944-1961) (Box 230, Folder 2))
  - Messiah— Photograph—Dec. 7, 1946—Community Chorus and Peabody Orchestra, Dr. Irving Wolfe, Conductor (Box 230, Folder 3))
  - Messiah— Programs—featuring Louis Nicholas, (1941, 1948, 1949, 1957, 1978) (Box 230, Folder 4))
  - Messiah— Reviews in The Tennessean (12-8-58; 12-4-61) of performances conducted by L. N. (Box 230, Folder 5))
  - Messiah— Programs, 1970-1995 (Box 230, Folder 6))
  - Messiah— Other programs (Box 230, Folder 7))
  - Messiah— Other programs (Box 230, Folder 8))
  - Messiah— Other programs (Box 230, Folder 9))
  - Messiah— 1954, 1955 Performance Notes by L.N. (Box 230, Folder 10))
  - Messiah— 1956 Performance Notes by L.N. (Box 230, Folder 11))
  - Messiah— 1957 Performance Notes by L.N. (Box 230, Folder 12))
  - Messiah— 1958 Performance Notes by L.N. (Box 230, Folder 13))
  - Messiah— 1960 Performance Notes by L.N. (Box 230, Folder 14))
  - Messiah— 1961 Performance Notes by L.N. (Box 230, Folder 15))
  - Messiah— Photograph—War Memorial Auditorium, Nashville, Tn (L.N. tenor, undated) (Box 230, Folder 16))
  - Nashville Arts Council—Calendar of Events, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, and others (Box 231, Folder 1))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Programs, 1936- Oct. 1971 (Box 231, Folder 2))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Programs, April 13, 1976—Nov. 27, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 3))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Programs, Feb. 9, 1980—Oct. 11, 1985 (Box 231, Folder 4))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Programs, Nov. 2, 1985—Nov. 10, 1989 (and undated) (Box 231, Folder 5))
  - Nashville Community Concerts Association—50 Years of Distinguished Service to the Community 1931-1981, List of Performances (Box 231, Folder 6))
  - Nashville Community Concerts Association—Lists of Performers 1931 (Box 231, Folder 7))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Promotional Materials and Membership cards (Box 231, Folder 8))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Membership Cards, 1975-76 Season (Box 231, Folder 9))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Constitution (Box 231, Folder 10))
  - Nashville Community Concerts Association--- 1958-71, 1980-81; Officers 1985-86; 1989-90; 1991 Letter Re: Louis Nicholas Concert (Box 231, Folder 11))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Membership Chairman, 1965-1968 (Box 231, Folder 12))
  - Nashville Community Concerts—Membership Chairman, 1966-1968 (Box 231, Folder 13))
  - Nashville Chamber Orchestra—1998-99; 1999-2000 Season (Box 231, Folder 14))
  - WPLN Advisory Board Committee and other WPLN information (Box 231, Folder 15))
  - WPLN FM—Public Radio—Information (Box 231, Folder 16))
  - WPLN FM—Public Radio—Notes on interview with Lin Folk on Madame Butterfly (Box 231, Folder 17))
  - Friends of Music—Programs, Promotional Materials, Financial Statement (Box 231, Folder 18))
  - Board of Directors (1988); Financial Statement (1983); Letter to the Editor (5-3-88) (Box 231, Folder 19) Friends of Music—Minutes of meetings (1988))
  - Music in Nashville—various programs (Box 231, Folder 20))
  - Music and Theater in Nashville—Programs—Ryman Auditorium—1927, 1935, 1936, others (Grand Ole Opry 1954) (Box 231, Folder 21))
  - Nashville Theater—Programs—Circle Players, 1970-1977 (Box 232, Folder 1))
  - Nashville Theater—Programs—Circle Players, 1981—1984 (Box 232, Folder 2))
  - Nashville Theater—Programs—Circle Players, 1985-1987 (Box 232, Folder 3))
  - Nashville Theater—Programs—Circle Players, Feb. 1998- May 12, 2002 (Box 232, Folder 4))
  - Nashville Theater—Circle Theater Players—Critic Information, 1985-1989 (Box 232, Folder 5))
  - Nashville Theater—Circle Players—Promotional Materials (Box 232, Folder 6))
  - Nashville Theater—Programs—Nashville Shakespeare Festival, 2000, 2001 (Box 232, Folder 7))
  - Nashville Theater—Programs—Act I, 1998-Feb. 9, 2002 (Box 232, Folder 8))
  - Nashville Theater—Programs (Box 232, Folder 9))
  - Tennessee Performing Arts Center; Nashville Pro Musica and others—Programs and Promotional Materials (Box 232, Folder 10))
  - Nashville Theater—Programs—Barn Dinner Theatre—1979-1987 (Box 232, Folder 11))
  - 2002 Annual Show “Have Harmony, Will Travel”—Program (Box 232, Folder 12))
  - Nashville Ballet—Programs and Promotional Materials (Box 232, Folder 13))
  - Nashville Ballet—Call Board, (1987- 1989) (Box 232, Folder 14))
  - and Promotional Materials, (March 1966) (Box 232, Folder 15) WSM—Correspondence)
  - Metro Nashville Schools—Lists of Music Teachers, 1974-1975 (Box 232, Folder 16))